Oh. Hey.
Hey.
I thought you and Alan
were going out to dinner.
We were supposed to,
but then he discovered
his coupon was only good
for to-go orders.
That guy's a piece of work.
He is.
Which is ironic,
'cause he never seems
to go to work. (laughs)
That's true.
That being said,
I do envy what
you guys have.
You guys are like termites.
Termites?
Yeah, they mate for life,
and once they live
in your house,
you can never get rid of 'em.
(chuckles)
(voice breaking):
Just like Alan.
You all right?
Yeah, I...
I have to do something
with him tonight
that's going to be
really painful.
Okay, that's between
two consenting adults.
No...
(sighs)
I'm breaking up
with him.
What?
No, but you guys are great
together.
You're so beautiful
and smart and fun and...
Alan's so...
lucky.
I don't want
to hurt him.
Then do something else.
Disneyland, dancing, bowling,
pretty much anything
but break up with him.
I have to.
But you and I are his world.
And if you leave,
I'll be his world.
I'm sorry.
No, I don't think
you heard me.
I'll. Be. His. World.
(crying):
I feel so bad.
(sobbing)
All right.
Come here.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
And I pushed a baby
out of my vagina.
(sobbing)
ALAN:
I'm back!
(gasps, sniffs)
Don't say anything.
Oh. Hey, Walden.
Want to join us?
Uh... no, thanks.
Hey, what do you say
we all go bowling?
Huh?
Doesn't that sound fun?
Just bowling?
No, I... I think we're
just gonna stay in tonight.
Uh... oh, but I have
a confession to make.
I, uh, opened my fortune
cookie in the car...
and listen to this:
uh... "your life is about to
take a turn for the better."
I think you may have gotten
Lyndsey's cookie.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 10x21 ♪
Another Night With Neil Diamond
Original Air Date on April 25, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Would you like another
glass of wi...?
Yes.
Oh, you know,
I was thinking, uh...
after dinner we could
light a fire.
Don't worry, I've got all
the wood we'll need.
Cute.
Just, uh... you seem
awfully quiet tonight.
Is everything okay?
I-I've just got
a lot on my mind.
Hmm, what is it,
sweetie?
Oh, boy.
I don't know
how to say this.
Well, a problem shared is
a problem halved.
It's kind of like
that fried rice,
although I noticed
you didn't touch your half,
despite the fact
that you had to order it,
even though
the white rice is free
and the coupon specifically
said "no substitutions."
I think we should break up.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
You owe me $22.50 for dinner.
Hey, Berta.
Just finishing up.
Then I'll get out of your way.
No, I think
you should stay here.
All right.
Let me take
a quick shower first.
No.
Lyndsey's downstairs breaking up
with Alan.
Really?
Yeah.
Well... we knew this was coming.
First time I saw them together,
I asked her to blink twice
if she was being held hostage.
He's gonna be devastated.
I mean, he's madly
in love with her,
they've been dating for years,
they were planning
on getting married.
Oh, my God,
he's never gonna leave my house.
It's sweet that you actually
thought he was going to.
Why do people have to break up?
Well, in my experience,
either the magic wears off,
or the mushrooms.
I feel really bad for him.
I mean,
I always feel bad for him.
But I feel really bad for him.
Yeah, yeah. It's tough.
We gonna do this thing
or what?
I don't understand.
Where is this coming from?
There's no spark anymore.
All we do is sit around,
watch TV and eat takeout
from whatever restaurant
you have a coupon for.
Did you want to go
to the food court?
'Cause we can do that.
Alan, it's not that.
Then, what is it?
I mean, I-I...
I thought you were happy.
I-I thought
everything was great.
It was, but, but things
change, people change.
That's not true.
I don't change. I never change.
Maybe that's part
of the problem.
I can change.
I-I know this is upsetting,
but, but better to do this
now before it gets worse.
How can it be worse?
You gonna tell me you've been
faking it all these years?
Don't answer that.
Alan, I have to go.
Fine, go.
Don't go.
I-I'm really sorry.
The thing is, I-I
still love you, Alan.
I'm just not in love
with you anymore.
It's not a deal-breaker.
You okay?
I guess.
I suppose it's better that
she broke up with me now
than after we got married.
Then she would've gotten
half of all my stuff.
Sure.
You know I'm
here for you.
I know that and,
and I appreciate it.
But... I'm good.
Good.
Walden?
Yeah?
(sobbing):
I'm not good.
I love her.
(sobbing)
I know you do.
I'll never find another one
like her.
I know you won't.
I-I'm just saying, I-I
know how great she is.
(grunts)
You're gonna be fine.
Just... you have to focus on
the good things in your life.
Lyndsey was the only
good thing in my life.
(sobbing): Oh, God...
It's okay.
(sobbing loudly)
Let it all out.
(Alan wails)
(sobbing noisily)
That's a lot out.
Let's-let's put some back in.
(Alan wails)
Now you're all I have!
(Alan sobbing)
(Walden sobbing)
(sobbing):
I know.
Good morning.
Beautiful day.
To... stick your head
in an oven?
Okay, I realize I was a
little upset last night.
A little?
You Googled "how to kill
yourself without it hurting."
(singsongy):
Drama queen.
But I woke up
this morning
and I realized, "What
am I so upset about?"
Lyndsey and I are
not breaking up.
Okay.
So, when she said that she
didn't want to see you anymore
and she didn't think you made
a good couple
and she wasn't in love with you,
that...
What do you call that?
Foreplay.
Okay. Looks like someone's
starting the day
with a hot, steaming cup
of denial.
No, no, no. This is a little
dance we do all the time.
She decides that
I did something wrong
and gives me the business,
and then I apologize,
and I give her the business.
Okay, see, that right there?
That's why she broke up
with you.
I'm telling you,
we are not broken up.
Okay, I see what
you're doing here,
but pretending like what
happened didn't happen
won't make it not happen,
no matter what you would like
to have had happened.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, thank you,
I appreciate it.
But if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go get my girl back.
Okay.
Just in case,
I'll preheat the oven.
(doorbell rings)
Alan?
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
That's what I love about you.
Okay, let's do this.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing
to be sorry about.
Our relationship just
isn't going anywhere.
All right, all right. Message
received, loud and clear.
Now let's get down to bidness.
Alan, it's over.
But... but why?
I-It just is.
Is it because we don't
like the same things?
'Cause I can learn
to love sports.
It has nothing
to do with that...
Is it, is it
because I'm-I'm frugal?
'Cause okay, watch this.
I am going to rip a twent--
a five-dollar bill in half.
Okay?
Tell me that's not sexy.
Okay, look... (sighs)
I didn't want
to have to say this,
but the fact of the matter is...
I've met someone else.
Oh. Wow.
Wow. Uh...
World spinning,
uh, gut tightening,
vomit rising... um...
I'm really sorry.
Well, well, who is he?
What's the difference?
Well, I-I need to know
who my competition is.
I-I need to know how I can win.
You can't win.
Good-bye, Alan.
(laughing)
Well, I have got
news for you.
The word "win" is not
in my vocabular...
"Can't."
The word "can't" is not
in my vocabulary.
Damn it.
(screams)
Son of a bitch!
(kicks)
(screams)
Of course.
Dog crap.
(grunts)
Hey, there's soup on the stove
if you want some.
I wonder if Lyndsey's
new boyfriend likes soup.
He probably loves soup.
And wears cable knit sweaters.
"Look at me,
I'm eating soup
"and wearing a sweater
while I bang the memory
of Alan Harper
out of this woman's mind."
(fake chuckles)
Alan, let it go.
You brought it up.
I brought up soup.
I can't stop thinking about him.
And her...
and what they're doing.
And what position
they're doing it in.
And where they're doing it.
In the bed, in the shower,
at the Costco
between the meat and the tires.
That was our place!
That shouldn't be
anyone's place.
And you're obsessing.
No, I'm not.
Right, we all picture
our exes screwing
between a rump roast
and a snow tire.
You know what,
I-I'm gonna go for a drive.
Where?
Just out, you know, joyride.
I've seen your car,
there's no joy in that ride.
Now where are you going?
I'm just gonna drive
up the coast a little bit.
Take in the sea air.
How? Your windows
don't roll down.
Just the ones in the front. The
ones in the back don't roll up.
Good-bye.
I should buy him a new car.
So he can live in it.
♪ Men
All right.
Where are they?
(sighs) They're probably
watching sports right now.
"Hello, Lyndsey,
you don't mind if I watch
"this baseball game
in the nude, do you?
"Sure, you can kiss me
between the strikes
and I'll kiss you
between the balls."
(phone rings)
Oh.
Hey, Walden.
Yeah, I'm just, uh,
you know, taking a drive
down the Malibu coast,
trying to clear my head.
Yeah, now I'm, uh,
I'm walking on the beach.
Sand feels nice on my toesies.
(pounding)
(screams)
Walking on the beach, huh?
Are you stalking me?
Are you stalking Lyndsey?
I asked you first.
Look, this
is pathetic.
Sitting outside
a woman's house,
trying to catch of glimpse
of her through the window.
What kind
of person does that?
(pounding)
(both scream)
Hey, guys, what are we doing?
Playing a little peek-a-boo
with Lyndsey?
No.
Yes.
Lyndsey broke
up with Alan
and he's having a hard
time understanding.
Oh, well, one look
at the new guy
and you'd understand it.
What, you've seen him?
Oh, yeah.
Nick's gorgeous.
Kind of looks like Walden.
Aw, thank you.
Y-You know his name,
so you-you've met him?
Well, no,
but I've heard her yell it.
It's either Nick
or Oh, God, Right There.
Oh, that's it.
I got to see this Nick guy
for myself.
No, Alan, don't.
You're better than this.
We both know
that's not true!
Yeah, I feel for him.
It's got to be tough.
Yeah, no doubt.
You really are
a very handsome man.
Again... thank you.
It's not hard to imagine you
naked and cast in marble.
Getting weird, Herb.
Right.
All right.
Where are you, you homewrecker?
(crackling)
Oh...
(panting)
That's better.
(owl hoots)
(screams)
(thud)
Ugh.
Can this get any worse?
LYNDSEY:
Oh, God, Nick, right there!
ALAN:
Aw.
(beeping)
Lyndsey,
hey.
Hey,
I need your help.
You need my help getting
back together with Alan?
No. I need you to tell him
to stop calling, e-mailing,
and texting me.
Words and pictures.
Especially the pictures.
He's just upset.
He means well.
Really?
Does this picture look
like he means well?
Oh, dear God.
Is he lying on my kitchen table?
So, will you talk to him?
Sure, right after I burn
my kitchen table.
Thank you. By the way, you might
want to burn your bathtub, too.
(Alan grunting)
Oh, he's coming now.
Got to go.
(grunting)
Hey. There he is.
Looking good.
Ha-ha.
(grunts)
Where you going?
Lyndsey un-friended me
on Facebook.
So I'm going to go
re-friend her with my face.
No, you're not.
You can't stop me.
Damn you.
(knocking)
Hey, Zip.
Oh, what do you want?
A motorcycle and another night
with Neil Diamond.
But for now we need to talk.
I just want to be left alone.
Like I'm gonna be
for the rest of my life.
Look, Lyndsey's crazy
for breaking up with you.
You are a great guy.
You're just saying that.
I know I'm rough on you,
but that's just for fun.
I really mean this.
Oh, thank you.
All right,
good talk.
How?
What?
How am I a great guy?
(sighs)
Well, you're
punctual.
I-I do make it
a priority to be on time.
Yep.
What else?
(sighs)
Okay.
You have pretty good toilet aim.
And that's important
to a housekeeper.
My secret is, I sit down.
And that should've
stayed a secret.
Take care.
Berta?
(sighs)
What?
I-I-If I'm such
a great guy,
then why did
Lyndsey leave me?
Oh, there's no telling
with chicks.
But don't worry...
you'll find somebody else.
As good as Lyndsey?
(chuckles)
Look at you,
already making jokes.
How'd it go?
He's gonna die alone.
And he pees sitting down.
I really don't want
to be here, Walden.
What are you
talking about?
You're doing great.
You shaved,
you showered.
You realized wearing
Lyndsey's underwear
wasn't a
long-term solution.
I may have it together
on the outside,
but on the inside
I'm still a wreck.
I just want to go home and
eat ice cream on the toilet
until I fall asleep.
Would you listen
to yourself?
Trust me, tonight
is going to be fun.
Okay. But if it's not,
you're gonna have to watch
The Notebook with me.
Really? Again?
WOMAN:
Walden.
Oh, hey, Allie, hi.
This is, uh, my friend Alan
I was telling you about.
Hi, Alan.
Hello.
You two have
a lot in common.
Really?
You know your girlfriend's
new boyfriend, Nick?
Yeah.
I'm his
soon-to-be ex-wife.
I'll just
let you two talk.
Oh, oh... you know, I-I
can see what Walden's
trying to do here,
and he means well,
but, um, I-I don't know
that I'm emotionally
ready to jump
back into the relation...
How do you feel about revenge sex?
Big fan. I'll
get the check.
Well, well, well.
Look who's doing
the walk of shame.
More like the stride of pride.
Guess who heard
"Oh, God, right there"
multiple times last night?
Not Nick.
Well,
congratulations.
I'm very happy
for you.
I have you to thank you it.
Ah, I didn't do anything.
Well, tracking Allie down
couldn't have been easy.
It wasn't that hard.
When we were
outside Lyndsey's house,
she was parked right behind us.
Which is ironic,
because last night I was parked
behind her...
I got it, I got it.
I'm happy you're
feeling better.
Oh, yeah.
And let me tell you,
revenge sex is way better
than revenge masturbation.
Course, there's no reason
you can't do both.
Oh, God, why am I eating
on this table?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==